SERGE CHURKIN



289-501-7013



sergechurkin@gmail.com



/sergechurkin/



sergechurkin-ca



www.serge-web.com



Toronto, ON

CORE COMPETENCIES

Technical Skills:

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Sass
- Responsive design
- JavaScript
- API
- Github and Collaboration
- jQuery
- React.js
- Firebase
- Node.js

Additional Skills:

- Leadership
- Complex problem solving
- Project Management
- Customer service
- Communication, Presentations and Public Speaking

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Toronto | 2020

- Web Development Immersive Certificate (Bootcamp)
- Javascript
- Introduction to Web Development

Niagara College Canada, Niagara Falls, ON | 2016 - 2018

- International Business
 Management
- Tourism and Hospitality Management

PROFILE SUMMARY

Front End Web Developer who is passionate about building accessible and responsive web applications. I combine my background in large scale operations management and excellent communication skills with technical skillset to to create user-friendly web experiences.

PROJECTS

Tour Agency Inventory - React, Firebase | <u>View Live</u>
Recipe Generator - JavaScript, API, jQuery | <u>View Live</u>
Poll It Together - React, Firebase, Github, Collaboration | <u>View Live</u>
Country Quiz - JavaScript, SCSS | <u>View Live</u>

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Juno College of Technology Toronto, ON

Mar 2020 - Aug 2020

Student

- Completed Web Development Immersive Bootcamp and Javascript programs
- Developed 7 web applications in a fast-paced environment, 1 week turn around time and intensive daily class activities
- Collaborated with team-mates remotely, conducted continuous deployments, debugging, code reviews, critique, presented the projects

Fallsview Group of Hotels Niagara Falls, ON Night Audit Supervisor

May 2018 - Jan 2020

- Improved processing of daily financial and balancing reports from 5 to 1.5 hrs
- Maximized revenue and ensured 101% hotel occupancy of with 200 rooms by overselling, monitoring reservations and updating rates
- Supervised and trained 2 auditors, shared best practices and trained booking system and reporting

Night Auditor

Aug 2016 - May 2018

- Reconciled, audited and balanced accounts, prepared revenue reports in property with 600 rooms
- Checked in guests, answered the calls and instant messages and ensured high standard of service

TEZ TOUR Thailand Phuket, Thailand Regional Manager

Feb 2015 - Feb 2016

- Oversaw inbound tourism operations in the Phuket region, managed the team of 100 employees
- Developed strategies to implement sales targets and increased regional revenue by 20%
- Successfully maintained industry leadership image of the company among 200 local partner hotels and 25 tour suppliers